Rajesh Agrawal to
discuss long term investment options, the
first question of the state will be this,
look at the three day gap of actual, this
university so much and the increase of 4% in its volume
troubled the market so much
that the entire Film City
basket got refreshed and came to full moon in just 5 seconds,
what was your approach after the actual results, we called it infection,
now after this deep
that the national staff is interested,
Banerjee Shailendra ji, the rest of the
friends in the panel, you said it right that
when the results of HAL came, if you
remember once, a surge was seen after the results
and as soon as the volume figures showed that there was only
4% volume growth, only after that
a cut was seen and the
entire family is seeing the full brunt of it in the back
because there was support, everyone started feeling that in
almost all places the volume group will
not grow as much as expected,
especially from the rural side, pressure was seen in volume,
this is in its place, but if we
look at the valuation, then
in the last one and a half years  The kind of boom that has happened in 2019, the
volume increased from subscription to companies.
All the companies are subscribing to Hindustan Lever
and from here it will
prove to be a good investment opportunity for your people. But I would
like to add that if you look at all this turmoil,
ITC is such a big
company which is still trading at a PE of 10-12.
Other big names in this position are trading at 80
to 100. So there is a
huge gap in valuation. Dividend
will be good but Film City is also
growing very well and there can be a
lot of vibration. Despite this, if you
look at it, in the last few days,
friends, it was moving in a range, above 260, what is it, friend, it
is 240. I think here
also, if long term investors should buy. If you are a
long term investor, then
your profile pick in SSC J will be
ITC ok 234. On this you can say that the
damage has been the least in the last few days.
Well, look at this, on your skin, I
swear this Shivling is still above it.  And there is a
crack on some lines where
profit booking is quite serious right now, you yourself have Eicher
Motors 2613, I
click on it for nothing, and you had also done AB
on your mind, Eicher Motors to end here
and you see once, Maruti Suzuki
Eeco, Maruti Suzuki has come on your skin on this channel,
what should we think about this from a shopping perspective, let's talk about this,
Banna word - there is a cup and one in it
and you should understand that since 8th October till now the
entire June has been broken, now the
big ones here come around
720, so there is a scope of ₹10,
now you have to play it through put, shop
tweet, will you keep asking whether you
were here on this or not,
opening the chart around 18 thousand, large cap will be a little bit of it
and more news is Davison point because for a
long time, the bottom in the stock was around 7000 for the last 10 days, it is
important
that today  The stock is rapid, it has been trading in the middle, there
is pistachio below it, but still I will
wait a little more, let the stock
settle for a while, not 7490, after that buy
oil here, it is very important, that is why you should
take a position on the short side in a hurry, I do
not think that the price is right in the market,
so it is better to buy oil below the following Maruti Suzuki for 4 minutes
and after that you can
buy half a cup at the airport on the spot,
that will be excellent, rent packing position
features, the strongest call and put option
is of 125, you can buy it there, you can buy it
below 75, and its
price will be around 225, but still I will
wait for fifteen-twenty minutes, let
Maruti first settle below 2014, so
let's guarantee, you can
see a short position coming in front of you, after four consecutive
days of selling, perhaps taking a short position at this time,
report this much,
you may not find it favorable, let's see, for a few hours, where
we are already tracking long trade
and it seems to be giving you good points from the intraday low.  Yes, look,
bring it all.
Cholamandalam Investment and Finance
Manager, this has been a favorite counter and
here this morning Mayuresh Joshi sir also gave
you an opinion. You should
add it to your portfolio because there is only one
special Nifty component that you can see
tweeting strongly. That's why the
desire for this web space is very strong.
Cholamandalam Investment Finance 60843.
Once, Gaon sir takes his opinion on the scooter and
then you will see Rajesh Agarwal sir praising the features of the scooter.
Prakash ji, put Prakash, you are
a good investor and have very strong
support. For
three days around June 590, it dipped in the east and has
again turned red, but the
track is there, give it some time. 640, you
will see,
Rajesh Agarwal sir, some special features
of Cholamandalam Investment Finance that
you like. The
biggest feature is that the
management is very good. It belongs to this phone group. There is
no issue of corporate governance. And the way the
economy is gradually getting back on track,
I think  It is true that not only Cholamandalam but
other MB companies like
HDFC
Ltd, Bajaj Finserv, such companies will
remain very good, they
cannot take away forest rights. I am talking about banks,
if you look at it, there
are many statements, the
equity of insurance broking is expected to give very good numbers
and I think it can also
give at least 10-12 percent rise from the current level, it is a
very good company, better
Meghvanshi, if you see, the asset quality there is at par
with others,
so obviously you should try to buy this dip
and Date sir, please
show me another counter, it is very rarely discussed
and if there is any strongest balance sheet in this VLC space,
which has been
working in every cycle for the last 30 years,
that is Sundaram Finance, it is trading ₹40 above in front of you,
2515 and the all time which we have
tracked in scooter is around 270,
which you saw it was there, on
July 14, it is a very strong counter,
its  We discuss this very rarely but
externally it is a very strong stock,
let us for now focus beyond article calls and
fundamental calls and add
BJP to this, Neeraj ji, I have evening
duty today, it is late evening duty
and it is fun to do duty, Bablu ji, it is
very good, what are you
expecting from this percentage, so
tell me Abe Smith, so look, on a base of 10 thousand crores,
you are expecting that you will see a 14%
increase in profit, you will definitely see it
and this quarter should go very well for all the oil
companies, refining companies
because the
price is very big, the demand is very big, if
you look at it globally, very interesting things can be
seen here, so what we are looking at in
this, on the cotton quarter,
we think that if we look at the revenue, then
our estimate is of 1 lakh 60 thousand crores,
which is 6